

# **CONTACT ME**

- **L** +1 (734) 575-5699
- Wyandotte, Michigan, United States

# **EDUCATION**

Ba (HONS) Computer Games Technology University of Suffolk

October 2019

Applied Science & IT
Long road sixth form college

2013-2015

Linton village college

2008 - 2013

## **SKILLS**

C#	CSS
Java	Maya
Python	Unity
JavaScript	<b>Unreal Engine</b>
HTML5	Microsoft
.NET 6.0	Office
SQL	DevOps
'isual Studio	QX/SX

# **Dominic**Talbot

IT/Digital Engineer

## **ABOUT ME**

IT/Digital engineer with two years of experience, starting in local government, where I developed e-forms for the South Norfolk and Broadland Councils merger. At TOR Systems, I spent six months as a Junior CRM Developer, contributing to the deployment of a CRM solution for Trentham. I focused on integrating the Stripo email/ticket template creator and campaign wizard and supported email and SMS insights analysis. My expertise includes integration, scripting, and automation, along with training staff to enhance system usage.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE** -

#### Career Break

May 2024 - Present

## **Relocated to the United States**

- Studying full-stack web development with Codecademy, earning certifications in relevant technologies.
- Volunteering at Wyandotte City Hall ConneX TV Studio, assisting with media production.
- Enhancing programming proficiency through coding challenges on LeetCode and independent projects.

#### Junior Software Developer

2023-2024

## **TOR Systems | Stoke-On-Trent**

- Contributed to the successful deployment of the CRM solution for Trentham, enhancing visitor attraction experiences.
- Created and managed the Stripo email/ticket template creator and campaign wizard, integrating with the Sinch Mailgun API for efficient bulk email communication.
- Assisted in implementing various pages and features to display and analyze email and SMS insights.

#### IT/Digital Apprentice

2021 - 2023

## **South Norfolk and Broadland Councils | Norwich**

- Developed web forms using ASP.NET to replace old top-level forms with the new .NET framework.
- Utilized SX/QX skills to monitor, fix, and create middleware for council forms that were submitted. The middleware facilitates the integration of submitted records into databases such as Integra Centros, and Idox Uniform.
- Created quarterly ArcGIS maps to visualize and track the number of visitors to the council website in Norfolk, South Norfolk, and Broadland regions.
- Trained new employees on using the CMS (Content Management System) for the council's website and internet site, enabling them to create new content such as pages, downloads, and homepages.